Yes, so did you cry on your knees during rehearsals the day before?
Yes, I cried.
I cried?
I cried so hard that my eyes were all puffy.
From our point of view, should we mention this part?
Yes, of course.
Everyone was wondering which way to go.
It would be a problem if we put more pressure on them.
But we can't ignore it either, so we were wondering what to do.
Harukun, what did you do about your ex?
Is it me?
I wonder...
Hmmm...
Well...
I was probably a bit of a nieve, so I'd probably sink even lower under more pressure.
I think it's best to say, "It's probably fine.
It's not like people didn't notice that he was saying all kinds of things, but they were all very concerned about him, right?
Yes, now that I think about it, I feel like I really bothered him.
I don't think I was bothering them, but I don't think I knew that they were aware of me at that time.
That's how blind I was to the world around me.
That's how it turned out.
The staff explained to me very carefully what I should say to each person at this distance. The staff explained to each person in detail what they should say from this distance.
I felt again how grateful I was for their help.
And then the day of the competition came, and you had to do all 10 competitions by yourself.
To be honest, was it hard work, physically?
Physically, it was pretty tough.
When I get out there and do it, I'm totally exhausted, but when it's over, I'll be back the next time.
But after the competition, the next time you go backstage...
Backstage?
I had to move from backstage to the main stage.
It was pretty hard to move from one stage to another.
What do you mean by moving?
I don't want to tell you to dash.
But it was still hard.
No, I was dashing.
You were dashing?
But you were dashing.
Only Mr. Hagima was dashing.
That's right.
I see.
Otherwise, I couldn't make it in time.
The kids who do the next event are already on standby for the previous event.
They're already on standby.
Isn't that how it's usually done, even in gymnastics?
Even at school.
That's why everyone's already lined up.
Sometimes they're already outside.
It's like, "Oh no, we're in a hurry.
I had to hurry, so I kept running.
I was exhausted by the end.
Physically
It was tough.
But what's more, it wasn't like an athletic meet.
We had to put on our own performance.
That's right.
We started with a big medley.
From then on...
I'm going to say medley this time, too.
In the case of Staffurafes
That's why all the idols are doing it for the first time.
It's the first time to do it.
Everyone is learning something new at that moment.
All kinds of things.
But we have to do it.
And when we rehearse a little bit the day before.
It's not like we're going to start the show in a less-than-perfect state.
I'm already nervous.
I was thrilled.
I feel like I'm always...
It's a personal thing.
There's always a bento box for lunch.
And before the show, I can finish the whole thing.
I'm not the type of person who gets nervous.
I can eat even when I'm nervous.
But this time I was so nervous that I couldn't finish it.
Oh, wow.
I don't know...
And the people around me...
You know...
There are members who know you well, aren't there?
Yes, I do
Even people from other groups
Didn't you eat anything? Didn't you ever feel like that?
There.
No, I hid it so they wouldn't.
So they wouldn't know?
Yes, that's right.
We didn't want to make other people feel uncomfortable.
That's right.
We all have our own groups to take care of.
That's where I'm coming from.
I don't want to make it seem like I'm having a hard time because I'm alone.
I don't want to make them feel like they're alone.
So you had them show that it's tough because you're alone?
Yes, it's hard for everyone.
Everyone is different.
You know...
They're all their own people.
I'm only carrying my own burden
But they all carry their own burdens
But they also carry their own group on their shouldersI'm carrying my group on my back.
I think the weight is the same.
No, but it's more than enough.
If you want to say that evitine...
The weight is...
I don't know why it's so hard.
I didn't want to give the impression that it's a lot of work.
I didn't want it to be too obvious.
But that's how the group performed.
And then there were these 10 different competitions.
Which one made the biggest impression on you?
Impression?
I was impressed.
The most memorable one was the last relay.
The relay or the dash?
Yes, the dash was the most memorable.
The dash?
I think it was the shout-out challenge that made the difference.
Yes, I shouted.
It was loud.
I thought I could do it.
You were confident.
I was pretty confident.
I just barely beat Yuzu with the rain flash.
I won by one decibel or so.
I was confident.
I was the most relaxed I've ever been.
In this competition, you don't have to work hard to get a result.
That's right.
I knew I should just scream.
I feel like I don't have to think about it as much as other competitions.
I don't know, maybe I don't think about it as much as I do in other events.
Did you think about it in other competitions?
I thought about it.
I thought about how I have to show myself in dance too.
The same goes for monoboke.
Monoboke is, if we talk about arrangements...
Out of all the competitions, monoboke was by far the one you pushed the most.
That's right.
Even in monoboke, everyone worked very hard, and it was very interesting.
It was very interesting.
I thought it was important to show myself as much as possible.
I was under a lot of pressure the day before.
But as an idol...
I knew that I couldn't just do something and go home.
I knew that I couldn't just do it and go home.
I wanted people to remember that Kana Harima was there.
I wanted people to remember that there was a woman named Halima Kana.
It's becoming a very historical story now.
It's a big story now.
I'm trying to get people to remember that Halima Kana was here.
I'm trying to get people to remember.
I've been trying to figure out how to get Halima Kana to compete in every single event.
I've been thinking about it.
I think the loudest voice now is that if you're the champion, that's where you're going to be, and that's where Halima Kana was.
So I was able to relax a lot.
It was the most relaxing competition for me.
I feel like if I do my usual, I'll be able to get results.
I thought, "If I do it the way I always do, I can do it.
In fact, I did, you know.
And I heard that even behind the scenes people were saying, "Oh, it's definitely Harima.
Eva's vote?
Yes, even Mr. Mayama of Ebichu.
I heard that the Morisaki people said it was a sure bet.
That's how confident I was.
So if you ask me what impressed me the most...
I would have to say the dash.
The dash was the best.
I don't know... the warmth of STAPLA...
I felt the warmth of the team the most at the dash.
Really? What made you feel that way?
First of all, the dash was right after my performance, wasn't it?
So I was still in a state of intuition.
I was still in tears.
And then everyone lined up on stage while I was still crying.
And then the kids who were going to do the dash, it was the last event, so...
And they get three points.
Everyone was so nervous, and their team's score was at stake.
I'm sure they're filled to the brim.
But everyone's there to comfort you and tell you it's going to be okay.
They rubbed my back.
And afterwards, after the goal...
Everyone was so warm and welcoming to the Argie people.
They welcomed me so warmly.
I felt that I was not alone.
DASH left the strongest impression on me.
It's true that after that concert
It was like a victory run, wasn't it?
That's right.
A little bit.
So you're actually going to do it?
But it's the live performance that's important, isn't it?
Yes.
That's right.
All 11 groups...
We drew lots for all of them.
We drew them at 9:00 a.m.
There were a lot of people who said it was too much.
There were a lot of people who said it was too much to be done.There were a lot of people saying how much is too much.
It's all over the Internet.
I'm really serious.
Yes, sir.
It starts with Ebichu and ends with Harima-san.
You really pulled a 9:00.
I really pulled it off.
I had a great reaction that time, too.
I thought my heart would stop.
What do you mean?
Yes.
It was the third time I did it.
11th?
Like 11th.
I mean, I was surprised then, but...
I was really surprised.
Oh, shit.
I thought, "Which one?
But I was happy inside.
That part was a little...
I said, "Oh my God," but inside I was already embarrassed.
What? I said, "I can't do it, I can't do it.
I said, "Can't you take out too much?
But secretly, I was happy.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
Oh my God.
At the same time...
But at the same time, I was happy.
Then it's very important what you do.
Yes, it is.
So I was wondering what you guys were going to do.
We were doing Silhouette of Courage.
Yes.
The moment I said that.
The audience, which is not supposed to be vocal
I wasn't supposed to speak out, but the audience was buzzing.
It was a buzz, wasn't it?
It got a big "ooh" from the audience.
You decided to do this by yourself?
Yes, I did.
I had one choice.
I chose the Silhouette of Courage.
I didn't think of anything else.
I'll tell you why.
Why?
Well, when I joined Stardust...
The first group I was in was 3PJr.
And the song "Silhouette of Courage
is the song of my idol origins.
I thought it was the song of my idol origins.
It's not like going back to the basics.
It's because I was alone that I thought I should go back to the basics.
That's why I chose "Silhouette of Courage".
And the other one is
I'm in Honey Rocket, Au and Harimakana.
3PJr and I haven't even been to the Stapler festival.
Oooh.
So.
As a member of the group I've been a part of
I've always wanted to participate in the Staplerfest.
I want to be a member of 3PJr.
And the feelings of everyone in 3PJr.
I'm not so big that I can carry the feelings of all 3PJr members on my shoulders.
I hope I can carry the feelings of 26 people on my back.
I made a silhouette of courage.
And the audience cried the most.
They were crying the most.
That day
I'm so grateful.
Did you already know that, Mr. Halima?
That you could feel that kind of atmosphere in the hall?
Yes, I did.
When we first decided to do the Silhouette of Courage.
What kind of venue?
First of all, it was a bird.
What? After the battle of time, you're going to do Harima? I'm sure you're thinking, "No, no, no.
No, no, no, but it's a lottery.
The moment you see "Toki-Sen", you know it's "Tori Harima".
I don't know how the audience will react.
I don't know how the audience will react when I say "Silhouette of Courage".
I didn't know how the audience would react when I said "Silhouette of Courage".
I was really anxious.
But the moment I said "Silhouette of Courage
I could feel the atmosphere of the venue change completely.
I was really happy that the atmosphere changed in a good way.
I was really happy.
Because of that...
I could feel the joy of the audience.
The warmth of everyone's voice
I was filled with so many feelings.
I cried a lot and became a silhouette of courage
But thanks to that, I managed to sing the whole song by myself
I was able to finish the song by myself.
I'm really grateful to the staff and
I was so thankful for all the fans who loved the show.
Then, after that, the members of Namie Girls' First Union came out.
When they came out, didn't you go to hug them?
Yes, I did.Here we go.
You know...
I was relieved.
After fighting all this time alone?
Yes.
When the usual members came out, it was like, "Hurry up and get here.
I was relieved that everyone had arrived, but the most important thing was that I was relieved.
Was it Kojima-san who was so relieved that he went to give you a hug?
It was Hana-chan, wasn't it?
That's right.
Everyone was lined up for the MC position.
And Hana-chan thought she had to be at the MC position, and I saw her, and I went to hug her.
Is it like you could have hugged anyone?
No, no, no.
No, of course not.
It's just that you didn't want to go for Mr. Sasaki.
No, that's not it.
But in Namie's case, when she cries, it's usually Hana-chan who goes to hug her and I go to her.
Oh, really?
Yes, that's right.
Yes.
I cried during the last MC speech at the previous Namie concert, right after the breakup and everything.
I was so moved that I cried, and it was Hana-chan who comforted me.
I don't know what it is, but I go to Hana-chan.
Maybe I'm subconsciously relying on her.
She's the youngest in Namie's group, but she's the best.
And she seemed dependable.
That's right.
And then he did the stage by himself, and as Namie, he went to the dash at the end.
And when I dashed into the stage, everyone was waiting for me, right?
But, Mr. Harima, at the end, we all had that reward, that star, that big affirmation event, but how did you feel afterwards?
Well, I'm really grateful that I was featured so much.
I'm really glad that I was able to participate in such a wonderful event where I was warmly welcomed by all the fans and staff members, and I'm also very happy that I was able to participate in it.
I'm really glad that I was able to participate in such a wonderful event where I was warmly supported by the fans and the members of the staff.
I'm really glad that I was able to participate in such a wonderful event where I was warmly watched over by all the staff members, and I'm not afraid of anything in the future, but when I think about how I was able to do it all by myself, I feel stronger now.
What do you want to do as a solo idol HARIMAHANA in the future?
I'm still frustrated that I couldn't sing through my tears.
I didn't cry because of the performance.
If I cried because of the performance, that would be a great talent as an actress.
But if I could have cried during the performance, that would have been a great talent as an actress, but I really felt like I could only give that performance at that time.
I could have given it my all, but I also wanted to sing that wonderful song "Silhouette of Courage" to the best of my ability.
So I want to be a solo idol who can take revenge.
If I'm going to do it, I want to do it again in the best condition.
I want to do it better than this time.
I'll do my best to be that good.
I want to do my best.
There are a lot of idols in Stardust, but I think I'm having the hardest time right now.
Really. I'm making them work hard, too.
Thank you for all your hard work.
You have done a lot of things for us, such as holding idol singing sessions and reading single songs to us, but I would like to conclude by saying to those who are watching now.
Lastly, please say something to the people who are watching this now.
Well, I am really happy if people like me and support me.
Please continue to support me.
May I?
I'm embarrassed that people know how serious I am.
A little embarrassed?
Embarrassed. But the first part was serious.
I was going to do something about it here, but then I thought, what am I going to do?
No, it's a little embarrassing that they know I'm so serious.
No, they know. It's obvious.
You can't hide it?
I'm not hiding it, and that's a good thing, isn't it?
Thank you.
No, you can't do that. I mean, you can't be all serious all of a sudden, can you?
That's right. But my goal is to become a woman who is out of the ordinary.
That's a serious person's goal.
Please subscribe to our channel.